ILR School Faculty Minutes /3087
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Faculty Minutes
1946-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3087
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Minutes (administrative records).
Minutes of the ILR faculty meetings for the first 30 years of the school.
8439036
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3013: Christopher Lindley Papers /3052: John W. McConnell Papers /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /4001: Robert H. Ferguson Papers /4125: ILR School Office of Student Services Additional Records /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8439036
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1950-1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Minutes of the Faculty NYSSILR, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Minutes of the Faculty, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- NYSSILR Faculty Meetings '74-'75, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- NYSSILR Faculty Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)